Larry Harmon zine collection LSC.2376
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Kool Man: The Amazing Story of Robert Dupree - Portland, OR, 1996 (Box 13, Folder 2)
- Littlebig SIster - #1, Ontario, Canada, 1993 (Box 13, Folder 3)
- Littlebig Sister - #2, Ontario, Canada, 1993 (Box 13, Folder 3)
- Local Zine - #6, Thousand Oaks, CA, Undated (Box 13, Folder 3)
- Lonesome - Palestine, Texas, Undated (Box 13, Folder 3)
- Love & Hate - #4, San Francisco, CA, Undated (Box 13, Folder 3)
- Lumpen - Vol. 4, #3, Chicago, IL, 1995 (Box 13, Folder 3)
- Lunch Magazine - Vol. 2, #1, Phoenix, AZ, 1997 (Box 13, Folder 3)
- Library Bonnet - #2, Orange, CA, Undated (Box 13, Folder 4)
- Library Bonnet - #6, Orange, CA, Undated (Box 13, Folder 4)
- Lookout - #31, Laytonville, CA, Summer 1988 (Box 13, Folder 5)
- Lookout - #33, Laytonville, CA, Summer 1989 (Box 13, Folder 5)
- Lookout - #35, Berkeley, CA, Summer 1991 (Box 13, Folder 5)
- Lookout - #36, Berkeley, CA, Winter 1992 (Box 13, Folder 5)
- Lookout - #37, Berkeley, CA, Summer 1992 (Box 13, Folder 5)
- Lookout - #38, Berkeley, CA, Winter 1993 (Box 13, Folder 5)
- Lookout - #39, Berkeley, CA, Summer 1994 (Box 13, Folder 5)
- Mazel-Tov Cocktail - New York City, NY, 1995 (Box 13, Folder 5)
- Modern Monuments - New York City, NY, 1997 (Box 13, Folder 5)
- Moonshine - #15, Portland, OR, 2001 (Box 13, Folder 5)
- Motion Sickness - #5, St. Louis, MO, Fall 1997 (Box 13, Folder 5)
- Motorbooty - #6, Detroit, MI, Fall 1992 (Box 13, Folder 5)
- Motorbooty - #7, Detroit, MI, Fall 1994 (Box 13, Folder 5)
- Mudflap - #5, San Francisco, CA, Undated (Box 13, Folder 5)
- Mudflap - #6, San Francisco, Undated (Box 13, Folder 5)
- Mad Planet - #1, Staten Island, NY, Undated (Box 13, Folder 6)
- Mad Planet - #2, Staten Island, NY, 1993 (Box 13, Folder 6)
- Mad Planet - #3, Staten Island, NY, 1993 (Box 13, Folder 6)
- Maximum Rock N Roll - #16, Berkeley, CA, August 1984 (Box 13, Folder 7)
- Maximum Rock N Roll - #143, San Francisco, CA, April 1995 (Box 13, Folder 7)
- Maximum Rock N Roll - #144, San Francisco, CA, May 1995 (Box 13, Folder 7)
- Maximum Rock N Roll - #146, San Francisco, CA, July 1995 (Box 14, Folder 1)
- Maximum Rock N Roll - #147, San Francisco, CA, August 1995 (Box 14, Folder 1)
- Maximum Rock N Roll - #148, San Francisco, CA, September 1995 (Box 14, Folder 1)
- Maximum Rock N Roll - #149, San Francisco, CA, October 1995 (Box 14, Folder 1)
- Maximum Rock N Roll - #150, San Francisco, CA, November 1995 (Box 14, Folder 1)
- Maximum Rock N Roll - #151 Part 1, San Francisco, CA, December 1996 (Box 14, Folder 1)
- Maximum Rock N Roll - #151 Part 2, San Francisco, CA, December 1995 (Box 14, Folder 1)
- Maximum Rock N Roll - #152, San Francisco, CA, January 1996 (Box 14, Folder 1)
- Maximum Rock N Roll - #154, San Francisco, CA, March 1996 (Box 14, Folder 1)
- Maximum Rock N Roll - #158, San Francisco, CA, July 1996 (Box 14, Folder 1)
- Maximum Rock N Roll - #159, San Francisco, CA, August 1996 (Box 14, Folder 1)
- Maximum Rock N Roll - #160, San Francisco, CA, September 1996 (Box 14, Folder 1)
- Maximum Rock N Roll - #161, San Francisco, CA, October 1996 (Box 14, Folder 1)
- Maximum Rock N Roll - #162, San Francisco, CA, November 1996 (Box 15, Folder 1)
- Maximum Rock N Roll - #163, San Francisco, CA, December 1996 (Box 15, Folder 1)
- Maximum Rock N Roll - #164, San Francisco, CA, January 1997 (Box 15, Folder 1)
- Maximum Rock N Roll - #165, San Francisco, CA, February 1997 (Box 15, Folder 1)
- Maximum Rock N Roll - #166, San Francisco, CA, March 1997 (Box 15, Folder 1)
- Maximum Rock N Roll - #167, San Francisco, CA, April 1997 (Box 15, Folder 1)
- Maximum Rock N Roll - #168, San Francisco, CA, May 1997 (Box 15, Folder 1)
- Maximum Rock N Roll - #169, San Francisco, CA, June 1997 (Box 15, Folder 1)
- Maximum Rock N Roll - #170, San Francisco, CA, July 1997 (Box 15, Folder 1)
- Maximum Rock N Roll - #171, San Francisco, CA, August 1997 (Box 15, Folder 1)
- Maximum Rock N Roll - #172, San Francisco, CA, September 1997 (Box 15, Folder 1)
- Maximum Rock N Roll - #174, San Francisco, CA, November 1997 (Box 15, Folder 1)
- Maximum Rock N Roll - #175, San Francisco, CA, December 1997 (Box 15, Folder 1)
- Maximum Rock N Roll - #178, San Francisco, CA, March 1998 (Box 15, Folder 1)
- Maximum Rock N Roll - #182, San Francisco, CA, July 1998 (Box 16, Folder 1)
- Maximum Rock N Roll - #183, San Francisco, CA, August 1998 (Box 16, Folder 1)
- Maximum Rock N Roll - #185, San Francisco, CA, October 1998 (Box 16, Folder 1)
- Maximum Rock N Roll - #186, San Francisco, CA, November 1998 (Box 16, Folder 1)
- Maximum Rock N Roll - #188, San Francisco, CA, January 1999 (Box 16, Folder 1)
- Maximum Rock N Roll - #189, San Francisco, CA, February 1999 (Box 16, Folder 1)
- Maximum Rock N Roll - #190, San Francisco, CA, March 1999 (Box 16, Folder 1)
- Maximum Rock N Roll - #191, San Francisco, April 1999 (Box 16, Folder 1)
- Maximum Rock N Roll - #205, San Francisco, CA, June 2000 (Box 16, Folder 1)
- Maximum Rock N Roll - #206, San Francisco, CA, July 2000 (Box 16, Folder 1)
- Maximum Rock N Roll - #207, San Francisco, CA, August 2000 (Box 16, Folder 1)
- Maximum Rock N Roll - #208, San Francisco, CA, September 2000 (Box 16, Folder 1)
- Maximum Rock N Roll - #250, San Francisco, CA, March 2004 (Box 16, Folder 1)
- Maximum Rock N Roll - #284, San Francisco, January 2007 (Box 16, Folder 1)
- Maximum Rock N Roll - #311, San Francisco, April 2009 (Box 16, Folder 1)
- Maximum Rock N Roll & Trust - Berkeley, CA and Augsburg, Germany, Undated (Box 17, Folder 1)
- Monozine - #4, Reisterstown, Maryland, 1997 (Box 17, Folder 2)
- Monozine - #5, Reisterstown, Maryland, 1998 (Box 17, Folder 2)
- Monozine - #6, Reisterstown, Maryland, 1999 (Box 17, Folder 2)
- Mudflap - 'Fraid a Who? San Francisco, CA, Undated (Box 17, Folder 3)
- Mudflap - Sex, Bikes, & Punx, San Francisco, CA, Undated (Box 17, Folder 3)
- Mudflap - #5, San Francisco, CA, Undated (Box 17, Folder 3)
- Multiball - #16, Portland, OR, 1999 (Box 17, Folder 4)
- Multiball - #18, Portland, OR, 1999 (Box 17, Folder 4)
- Multiball - #19, Portland, OR, 2000 (Box 17, Folder 4)
- Multiball - #20, Portland, OR, 2000 (Box 17, Folder 4)
- Music 619 Magazine - Vol. 1, #2, San Diego, CA, March / April 1993 (Box 17, Folder 5)
- Music 619 Magazine - Vol. 1, #4, San Diego, CA, July / August 1993 (Box 17, Folder 5)
- Music 619 Magazine - Vol. 1, #5, San Diego, CA, September / October 1993 (Box 17, Folder 5)
- Nardwuar The Human Serviette vs Bev Davies Calendar, 2007 (Box 27, Folder 3)
- No Loitering - #7, Lawrence, KS, 1988 (Box 17, Folder 6)
- No Idea - #7, Gainesville, FL, 1989 (Box 17, Folder 7)
- No Idea - #8, Gainesville, FL, 1991 (Box 17, Folder 7)
- No Idea - #10, Gainesville, FL, 1991 (Box 17, Folder 7)
- No Idea - #11, Gainesville, FL, 1993 (Box 17, Folder 7)
- One More Time Around - San Diego, CA, Undated (Box 17, Folder 8)
- 32 Stories (Complete Optic Nerve) - Montreal, Quebec, 1995 (Box 17, Folder 8)
- Optic Nerve - #1, Berkeley, CA, 1991 (Box 17, Folder 8)
- Optic Nerve - #2, Berkeley, CA, 1991 (Box 17, Folder 8)
- Optic Nerve - #3, Sacramento, CA, 1992 (Box 17, Folder 8)
- Optic Nerve - #4, Berkeley, CA, 1992 (Box 17, Folder 8)
- Optic Nerve - #5, Sacramento, CA, 1993 (Box 17, Folder 8)
- Omnibus of Fun - #8, San Francisco, CA, 1999 (Box 17, Folder 9)
- Omnibus of Fun - #11, San Francisco, CA, 2003 (Box 17, Folder 9)
- Ox Fanzine - #34, Essen, Germany, 1999 (Box 25, Folder 3)
- Popart 'Zine - Fredonia, NY, Undated (Box 17, Folder 10)
- Pinguono & Pedestrian, 2003 (Box 17, Folder 10)
- Pistil Prose - #3, Seattle, WA, 1997 (Box 17, Folder 10)
- Powell Peralta - Santa Barbara, CA, Undated (Box 17, Folder 10)
- Psychotronic - #19, Narrowsburg, NY, 1994 (Box 17, Folder 10)
- PTBH! - #10, Seattle, WA, Undated (Box 17, Folder 10)
- Pulp - #4, Olympia, WA, Undated (Box 17, Folder 10)
- Panic Button - #6, Prospect Heights, IL, 1992 (Box 18, Folder 1)
- Panic Button - #8, Prospect Heights, IL, 1993 (Box 18, Folder 1)
- Panic Button - #9, Prospect Heights, IL, 1994 (Box 18, Folder 1)
- The Probe - #1, Pleasanton, CA, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 2)
- The Probe - #2, Pleasanton, CA, 1992 (Box 18, Folder 2)
- The Probe - #4, Pleasanton, CA, 1994 (Box 18, Folder 2)
- The Probe - #5, Pleasanton, CA, 1995 (Box 18, Folder 2)
- The Probe - #8, Pleasanton, CA, 1999 (Box 18, Folder 2)
- Profane Existence - #11/12, Minneapolis, MN, Autumn 1991 (Box 18, Folder 3)
- Profane Existence - #24, Minneapolis, MN, January - March 1995 (Box 18, Folder 3)
- Profane Existence - #29/30, Minneapolis, MN, 1996 (Box 18, Folder 3)
- Punk Rock Confidential - #1, San Francisco, CA, 2005 (Box 18, Folder 4)
- Punk Rock Confidential - #2, San Francisco, CA, 2005 (Box 18, Folder 4)
- Punk Rock Confidential - #3, San Francisco, CA, 2005 (Box 18, Folder 4)
- Punk Rock Confidential - San Francisco, CA, Spring 2007 (Box 18, Folder 4)
- Punk Rock Confidential - San Francisco, CA, Summer 2008 (Box 18, Folder 4)
- Punk Rock Confidential - San Francisco, CA, Winter 2008 (Box 18, Folder 4)
- Punk Planet - #1, Hoboken, NJ, May / June 1994 (Box 18, Folder 5)
- Punk Planet - #2, Hoboken, NJ, August 1994 (Box 18, Folder 5)
- Punk Planet - #3, Hoboken, NJ, September / October 1994 (Box 18, Folder 5)
- Punk Planet - #30, Chicago, IL, March / April 1999 (Box 18, Folder 5)
- Punk Planet - #31, Chicago, IL, May / June 1999 (Box 18, Folder 5)
- Punk Planet - #33, Chicago, IL, September/October 1999 (Box 18, Folder 5)
- Rational Inquirer - #8, Hialeah, FL, 1997 (Box 18, Folder 6)
- Retrieval Incorporated - #1, Ocean City, NJ, Undated (Box 18, Folder 6)
- Rev. Richard J. Mackin's Book of Letters - #11, Allston, MA, 1998 (Box 18, Folder 6)
- Rich and Bone - #2, San Diego, CA, Undated (Box 18, Folder 6)
- Roommate Stories - Vol. 1, #1, Hayward, CA, Undated (Box 18, Folder 6)
- Rats in the Hallway - #12, Boulder, CO, 1999 (Box 18, Folder 7)
- Razorcake - #2, Los Angeles, CA, June / July 2001 (Box 19, Folder 1)
- Razorcake - #4, Los Angeles, CA, October / November 2001 (Box 19, Folder 1)
- Razorcake - #7, Los Angeles, CA, April - May 2002 (Box 19, Folder 1)
- Razorcake - #13, Los Angeles, CA, April / May 2003 (Box 19, Folder 1)
- Razorcake - #15, Los Angeles, CA, August / September 2003 (Box 19, Folder 1)
- Razorcake - #24, Los Angeles, CA, February / March 2005 (Box 19, Folder 1)
- Razorcake - #26, Los Angeles, CA, June / July 2005 (Box 19, Folder 1)
- Razorcake - #27, Los Angeles, CA, August / September 2005 (Box 19, Folder 1)
- Razorcake - #32, Los Angeles, CA, June / July 2006 (Box 19, Folder 1)
- Razorcake - #33, Los Angeles, CA, August / September 2006 (Box 19, Folder 1)
- Razorcake - #34, Los Angeles, CA, October / November 2006 (Box 19, Folder 1)
- Razorcake - #35, Los Angeles, CA, December 2006 / January 2007 (Box 19, Folder 1)
- Razorcake - #37, Los Angeles, CA, April / May 2007 (Box 19, Folder 1)
- Razorcake - #38, Los Angeles, CA, June / July 2007 (Box 19, Folder 1)
- Razorcake - #39, Los Angeles, CA, August / September 2007 (Box 19, Folder 1)
- Razorcake - #40, Los Angeles, CA, September / October 2007 (Box 19, Folder 1)
- Razorcake - #42, Los Angeles, CA, February / March 2008 (Box 19, Folder 1)
- Razorcake - #43, Los Angeles, CA, April / May 2008 (Box 19, Folder 1)
- Razorcake - #44, Los Angeles, CA, June / May 2008 (Box 19, Folder 1)
- Razorcake - #57, Los Angeles, CA, August / September 2010 (Box 20, Folder 1)
- Razorcake - #80, Los Angeles, CA, June / July 2014 (Box 20, Folder 1)
- Razorcake - #104, Los Angeles, CA, June / July 2018 (Box 20, Folder 1)
- Razorcake - #105, Los Angeles, CA, August / September 2018 (Box 20, Folder 1)
- Razorcake - #106, Los Angeles, CA, October / November 2018 (Box 20, Folder 1)
- Razorcake - #136, Los Angeles, CA, October / November 2023 (Box 20, Folder 1)
- Razorcake - #139, Los Angeles, CA, April / May 2024 (Box 20, Folder 1)
- Razorcake - #142, Los Angeles, CA, October / November 2024 (Box 20, Folder 1)
- Reality Control? - #5, Carpinteria, CA, Undated (Box 20, Folder 2)
- Reality Control? - #6, Carpinteria, CA, 1992 (Box 20, Folder 2)
- Reality Control? - #9, Carpinteria, CA, Undated (Box 20, Folder 2)
- Roctober - #24, Chicago, IL, 1999 (Box 20, Folder 3)
- Roctober - #26, Chicago, IL, 2000 (Box 20, Folder 3)
- Roctober - #28, Chicago, IL, 2000 (Box 20, Folder 3)
- Roctober - #35, Chicago, IL, 2003 (Box 20, Folder 3)
- Roller Derby - #5, Dover, NH, 1992 (Box 20, Folder 3)
- Roller Derby - #6, Dover, NH, 1992 (Box 20, Folder 3)
- Roller Derby - #13, Dover, NH, Undated (Box 20, Folder 3)
- Semigloss - #3, Miami Beach, FL, 1996 (Box 20, Folder 4)
- SG (Surf Snow Skate Girl Magazine) - Vol. 6, #3, San Clemente, CA, June / July 2003 (Box 20, Folder 4)
- Shelf Life - #4, Santa Barbara, CA, Undated (Box 20, Folder 4)
- Shooting Space - #1, Richmond, VA, 1997 (Box 20, Folder 4)
- Shit & Garbage - #2, Sherburne, NY, 1994 (Box 20, Folder 4)
- Silver City Magazine - Vol.2, June 2002 - April 2003 (Box 20, Folder 4)
- Sincere Brutality - #1, Portland, OR, 2002 (Box 20, Folder 4)
- Slate Skate - #1, Lexington, Kentucky, 1987 (Box 20, Folder 4)
- Slug & Lettuce - #72, Richmond, VA, 2002 (Box 20, Folder 4)
- Slutburger - #3, Montreal, Canada, 1993 (Box 20, Folder 4)
- Sneezing Jesus - #7, Sherburne, NY, Undated (Box 20, Folder 4)
- Spontaneous Combustion - #15, Downers Grove, IL, 1993 (Box 21, Folder 1)
- Spontaneous Combustion - #16, Downers Grove, IL, 1994 (Box 21, Folder 1)
- Stab! Stab! Stab! - Austin, Texas, 1992 (Box 21, Folder 1)
- SteamPunk Magazine - Issue 2, Portland, OR, 2007 (Box 21, Folder 1)
- Sticky Fingers - #5, Olympia, WA, Undated (Box 21, Folder 1)
- Sound Choice - #11, Ojai, CA, 1989 (Box 21, Folder 1)
- Sourball Prodigy - #2, Largo, FL, 1992 (Box 21, Folder 1)
- Stroker - #2, San Francisco, CA, 2002 (Box 21, Folder 1)
- Subspace - Iowa City, IA, 1992 (Box 21, Folder 1)
- Sunburn - #2, Tempe, AZ, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 1)
- Superfly - #1, Bensenville, IL, 1993 (Box 21, Folder 1)
- Scam - #1, Fort Lauderdale, FL, 1991 (Box 21, Folder 1)
- Scam (reissue) - #1, Miami, FL, 2001 (Box 21, Folder 2)
- Scam - #2, Miami, FL, 1993 (Box 21, Folder 2)
- Scam - #3, Torrance, CA, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 2)
- Scam - #4, Berkeley, CA, 2000 (Box 21, Folder 2)
- Scam - #5, San Francisco, CA, 2005 (Box 21, Folder 2)
- Scam - #5 1/2, San Francisco, CA, 2006 (Box 21, Folder 2)
- Scam - #6, San Francisco, CA, 2006 (Box 21, Folder 2)
- Scam - #7, Brooklyn, NY, 2010 (Box 21, Folder 2)
- Schlock - #23, San Diego, CA, Undated (Box 21, Folder 3)
- Schlock - #25, San Diego, CA, Undated (Box 25, Folder 4)
- SCHtuff - #2, BC, Canada, 1994 (Box 21, Folder 4)
- SCHtuff - #3, BC, Canada, 1995 (Box 21, Folder 4)
- Scram - #6, Hollywood, CA, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 5)
- Scram - #7, Hollywood, CA, 1998 (Box 21, Folder 5)
- Scram - #9, Hollywood, CA, 1999 (Box 21, Folder 5)
- Scram - #15, Hollywood, CA, 2002 (Box 21, Folder 5)
- Scram - #17, Hollywood, CA, 2003 (Box 21, Folder 5)
- Scrape - #6, Miami, FL, 1992 (Box 22, Folder 1)
- Scrape - #7, Miami, FL, 1993 (Box 22, Folder 1)
- Scrape - #8, Miami, FL, 1993 (Box 22, Folder 1)
- Scrape - #9, Miami, FL, 1993 (Box 22, Folder 1)
- Scrape #10, Miami. FL, 1994 (Box 22, Folder 1)
- Scrape - #11, Miami, FL, 1994 (Box 22, Folder 1)
- Scrape - #12, Miami, FL, 1994 (Box 22, Folder 1)
- Second Guess - #11, Reno, NV, 1994 (Box 22, Folder 2)
- Second Guess - #12, Reno, NV, 1995 (Box 22, Folder 2)
- Second Guess - #13, Reno, NV, 1996 (Box 22, Folder 2)
- Shelf Life - #1, Santa Barbara, CA, 1993 (Box 22, Folder 3)
- Shelf Life - #2, Santa Barbara, CA, 1994 (Box 22, Folder 3)
- Sick To Move - Vol.3, #1, San Diego, CA, June 2000 (Box 22, Folder 4)
- Sick To Move - Vol.3, #4, San Diego, CA, September 2002 (Box 22, Folder 4)
- Slant - #7, Philadelphia, PA, 1996 (Box 25, Folder 5)
- Slant - #8, Philadelphia, PA, 1997 / 98 (Box 25, Folder 5)
- Slant - #9, Philadelphia, PA, 1997 (Box 25, Folder 5)
- Sleestk - #2, Seattle, WA, 1996 (Box 22, Folder 5)
- Sleestk - #3, Seattle, WA, 1996 (Box 22, Folder 5)
- Sleestk - #4, Seattle, WA, 1996 (Box 22, Folder 5)
- Sleestk - #6, Seattle, WA, 1997 (Box 22, Folder 5)
- Speed Kills! - #4, Chicago, IL, 1993 (Box 22, Folder 6)
- Speed Kills! - #5, Chicago, IL, 1993 (Box 22, Folder 6)
- Speed Kills! - #6, Chicago, IL, 1994 (Box 22, Folder 6)
- Speed Kills! - #7, Chicago, IL, 1995 (Box 22, Folder 6)
- spleen - #1, Jersey City, NJ, 1992 (Box 22, Folder 7)
- spleen - #2, Jersey City, NJ, 1992 (Box 22, Folder 7)
- Static - #1, San Francisco, CA, Summer 1996 (Box 22, Folder 8)
- Static - #2, San Francisco, CA, Winter 1996 (Box 22, Folder 8)
- Strange Notes - #2, Soquel, CA, September 1987 (Box 22, Folder 9)
- Strange Notes - Calendar, Soquel, CA, 1988 (Box 22, Folder 9)
- Strange Notes -#5, Soquel, CA, 1988 (Box 22, Folder 9)
- Strange Notes - #7, Soquel, CA, 1988 (Box 22, Folder 9)
- Strange Notes - #8, Soquel, CA, 1988 (Box 22, Folder 9)
- Suburban Voice - #22, Lynn, MA, 1987 (Box 23, Folder 1)
- Suburban Voice - #27, Lynn, MA, 1988 (Box 23, Folder 1)
- Suburban Voice - #28, Lynn, MA, 1989 (Box 23, Folder 1)
- Suburban Voice - #30, Lynn, MA, 1991 (Box 23, Folder 1)
- Suburban Voice - #31, Lynn, MA, 1991 (Box 23, Folder 1)
- Suburban Voice - #32, Lynn, MA, 1992 (Box 23, Folder 1)
- Suburban Voice - #33, Lynn, MA, 1993 (Box 23, Folder 1)
- Suburban Voice - #35, Lynn, MA, 1993 (Box 23, Folder 1)
- Tablet - Seattle, WA, 2002 (Box 23, Folder 2)
- Technology Works - #7, Placentia, CA, June 1991 (Box 23, Folder 2)
- Things - Tempe, AZ, 1994 (Box 23, Folder 2)
- things are meaningless - Portland, OR, 1997 - 1998 (Box 23, Folder 2)
- Tight Pants - #8, Amherst, MA, 2001 (Box 23, Folder 2)
- Tiki News - #10, San Francisco, CA, 1996 (Box 23, Folder 2)
- Touch and Go - McLean, VA, 1991 (Box 23, Folder 2)
- Trials & Tribulations of a Hollywood Nothing - #1, Los Angeles, CA, Undated (Box 23, Folder 2)
- Twistworthy - #5. Spring, Texas, 1992 (Box 23, Folder 2)
- Taste Like Chicken - #2, Santee, CA, 1993 (Box 23, Folder 3)
- Taste Like Chicken - Santee, CA, 1993 (Box 23, Folder 3)
- Tales of Blarg! - #4, Berkeley. CA, 1991 (Box 23, Folder 4)
- Tales of Blarg - #6, Berkeley, CA, 1993 (Box 23, Folder 4)
- Temp Slave - #5, Madison, WI, 1994 (Box 23, Folder 5)
- Temp Slave - #6, Madison, WI, 1994 (Box 23, Folder 5)
- Temp Slave - #7, Madison, WI, 1995 (Box 23, Folder 5)
- Temp Slave - #8, Madison, WI, 1996 (Box 23, Folder 5)
- Temp Slave - #9, Madison, WI, 1996 (Box 23, Folder 5)
- Temp Slave - #10, Madison, WI, 1996 (Box 23, Folder 5)
- Thicker - #1, San Francisco, CA, 1994 (Box 23, Folder 6)
- Thicker - #2, San Francisco, CA, 1994 (Box 23, Folder 6)
- Thicker - #4, San Francisco, CA, 1995 (Box 23, Folder 6)
- Thrift Score - #1, Pittsburgh, PA, Spring 1994 (Box 23, Folder 7)
- Thrift Score - #2, Pittsburgh, PA, Summer 1994 (Box 23, Folder 7)
- Thrift Score - #3, Pittsburgh, PA, Fall 1994 (Box 23, Folder 7)
- Thrift Score - #4, Pittsburgh, PA, Winter 1994 (Box 23, Folder 7)
- Thrift Score - #5, Pittsburgh, PA, Spring 1995 (Box 23, Folder 7)
- Thrift Score - #6, Pittsburgh, PA, 1995 (Box 23, Folder 7)
- Thrift Score - #7, Pittsburgh, PA, 1996 (Box 23, Folder 7)
- Thrift Score - #8, Pittsburgh, PA, 1996 (Box 23, Folder 7)
- Thrift Score - #9, Pittsburgh, PA, 1996 (Box 23, Folder 7)
- UGZ - #14, Berkeley, CA, 2003 (Box 23, Folder 7)
- Vice - Vol.18, #7, 2011 (Box 25, Folder 6)
- Wajlemac - #5, Larkspur, CA, Summer 1988 - Fall 1988 (Box 24, Folder 1)
- Xtra Tuf - #3, Portland, OR, 2001 (Box 24, Folder 2)
- You Bet Your Sweet Ass I'm a Turtle - #1, San Francisco, CA, 1993 / 1994 (Box 24, Folder 3)
- Your Flesh - #24, Minneapolis, MN, 1992 (Box 24, Folder 3)
- Your Flesh - #26, Minneapolis, MN, 1992 (Box 24, Folder 3)
- Your Flesh - #28, Minneapolis, MN, 1993 (Box 24, Folder 3)
- Your Flesh - #33, Minneapolis, MN, 1996 (Box 24, Folder 3)
- Your Ugly Mom's Ass - #4, Yuma, AZ, 1995 (Box 24, Folder 3)
- Yello Submarine - #1, Elmira, NY, 1993 (Box 24, Folder 4)
- Yello Submarine - #2, Elmira, NY, 1993 (Box 24, Folder 4)
- Yello Submarine - #3, Elmira, NY, 1993 (Box 24, Folder 4)
- Yello Submarine - #5, Elmira, NY, 1993 (Box 24, Folder 4)
- Yellow Sub - #7, Elmira, NY, 1994 (Box 24, Folder 4)
- Yellow Submarine - #9, Elmira, NY, 1994 (Box 24, Folder 4)
- yak'uz'a - #5, Wilmington, DE, 1994 (Box 24, Folder 5)
- yak'uz'a - #8, Wilmington, DE, 1996 (Box 24, Folder 5)
- yak'uz'a - #9, Wilmington, DE, 1997 (Box 24, Folder 5)
- Zapruder headSNAP - #9, San Francisco, CA, 1997 (Box 24, Folder 6)
- Zugang - #5, Richmond, IN, 1989 (Box 24, Folder 8)
- Zugang - #8, Richmond, IN, 1991 (Box 24, Folder 8)
- Zine Guide - #1, Evanston, IL, 1998 (Box 24, Folder 7)
- Zine Guide - #2, Evanston, IL, 1999 (Box 24, Folder 7)
- Zine Guide - #3, Evanston, IL, 2000 (Box 24, Folder 7)
- Zine Guide - #5, Evanston, IL, 2001 (Box 24, Folder 7)
- Zine Guide - #6, Evanston, IL, 2002 (Box 24, Folder 7)
- Zisk - #30, Patterson, NY, 2020 (Box 24, Folder 7)